{
    "subject": "Jan_Waters",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Peter_Gilmore",
    "human_readable": "Jan Waters is married to Peter Gilmore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988021194934845,
            "question": "Is Peter Gilmore married to Jan Waters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9862825274467468,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Jan Waters and Peter Gilmore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9816016554832458,
            "question": "Does Jan Waters have a spouse named Peter Gilmore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9528849124908447,
            "question": "Are Jan Waters and Peter Gilmore in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8960471749305725,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jan Waters and Peter Gilmore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803482055664062,
            "question": "To whom is Jan Waters married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8663535118103027,
            "question": "Who is Jan Waters married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783008337020874,
            "question": "Who is the husband of Jan Waters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5490394830703735,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter Gilmore's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5449095964431763,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter Gilmore's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jan Waters is married to Peter Gilmore.",
            "html": "yago_26535_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Peter Gilmore's wife?",
            "html": "yago_26535_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the husband of Jan Waters?",
            "html": "yago_26535_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Jan Waters married to?",
            "html": "yago_26535_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26535_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided support the triple that Jan Waters is married to Peter Gilmore. The relevant information can be found in files 51.txt, 59.txt, and 2.txt, which all mention that Jan Waters was once married to actor Peter Gilmore."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"She was once married to actor Peter Gilmore.\" referring to Jan Waters, which supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}